Contact

8508079137 (Mobile) su.ajeet@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ajeet-adeteea-1b5a05172 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Machine Learning
Data Science
Artificial Intelligence (AI)

Languages

French (Elementary)
Tamil (Full Professional)
English (Full Professional)

Certifications

Microsoft certified :Data Analyst Associate with PowerBI Business Analysis Fundamentals Financial Risk Analysis Business Analytics and Digital Media Deep Learning: Face Recognition

Ajeet Adeteea

Data Analyst | Decision Scientist | Ex-Bounce | Freelancer Bengaluru

Summary

Having a 8 months of experience working in Analytics and data science. Currently, I work as a Data Analyst at Kushal Jewellery, building reports and dashboards that are helping people achieve more in their growth!

Previously, I worked at Bounce Startup as a Jr Decision Scientist, improving products and services for our customers by using advanced analytics, setting up Automation (i.e. Python, Airflow), creating and maintaining models, and onboarding new data sets.

Competencies: Python, Machine Learning, PowerBI, Tableau, SQL, Keras, machine learning, TensorFlow, Business Intelligence, Time Series, Business Analysis, Prediction Analysis

Experience

Kushal's Fashion Jewellery Data Analyst July 2020 - Present (2 months) Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Inference Labs
Junior Decision Scientist
January 2020 - June 2020 (6 months)
Bengaluru, Karnataka

Worked directly for Bounce, Bangalore

The work is based on full stack Data Analytics which involves data analysis, data visualization, data extraction and taking strong business decisions based on the trends. Work is on client location permanently and the client is the world's fastest growing scooty rental company and is one of a kind start up in terms of its services.

Tools worked on : | Python | SQL | Tableau | Business Analysis | Prediction
Analysis | Data Studio | Data Airflow | Automation | Google sheet |
Page 1 of 2

NLC India Limited Inplant Training August 2017 - October 2017 (3 months) Neyveli, Tamil Nadu

Vellore Institute of Technology 2 years 1 month Student Coordinator August 2016 - July 2017 (1 year) Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India

Event Manager July 2015 - July 2016 (1 year 1 month) Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India

Bharat Sanchar Nigam Limited Summer Trainee April 2016 - June 2016 (3 months) Chennai, Tamil Nadu

Education

Great Lakes Institute of Management

Post Graduate Program, Data science Machine Learning · (2018 - 2019)

Vellore Institute of Technology
BTech - Bachelor of Technology, Electrical and Electronics
Engineering · (2014 - 2018)

Narayana Junior College , Nellore
INTERMEDIATE, Higher Education · (2012 - 2014)

Central Board of Secondary Education (2008 - 2012)